hard69.com 2008-09-08

# Privacy Policy

**Our Commitment**

We take your privacy seriously. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about your personal information. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our web site including where personally identifiable information may be submitted. 

**What this Privacy Policy Covers**

This Privacy Policy covers our treatment of all personally identifiable information collected or submitted on our site and your use of our services including ordering subscriptions, user feedback submissions, surveys, making requests or registering to receive materials from time to time. This Privacy Policy also covers our treatment of all personally identifiable information that our business partners share with us. 

**Information Collection and Use**

  * We collect personally identifiable information when you subscribe for our site and when you communicate with us about your subscription. We may also receive personally identifiable information from our business partners. 
  * When you subscribe or communicate with us, we ask for your email address and you are automatically added to a list of email recipients who receive information about related specials, updates, promotions, new products and services. 
  * We also automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, "cookie" information and the web page(s) you requested. 
  * We use information for three general purposes: (i) to customize the advertising and content you see, (ii) to fulfill your requests for services, and (iii) to contact you regularly about related specials, updates, promotions, new products and services. 

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

  * We will send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or organizations when:
    * We need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested;   

    * We need to send the information to companies who work on behalf of us to provide a product or service to you;   

    * We respond to subpoenas, court Orders or legal process; or   

    * We find that your actions on our web site violate our Terms of Use, if any.   

**Unsubscribe**

  * If you do not wish to be contacted regularly about related specials, updates, new products and services, you may unsubscribe from the list of email recipients by entering your email at http://www.hard69.com/unsubscribe/. 

**Cookies**

  * We may set and access cookies on your computer. 
  * We allow other companies that are presenting advertisements on our web site to set and access their cookies on your computer. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

  * We may amend this policy from time to time. 
  * This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that we do not own or control, or to people that we do not employ or manage. 

**Our Commitment to Data Security**

  * To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place reasonably appropriate procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

**How You Can Correct Your Information**

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows an error. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before making corrections. 

**How To Contact Us**

  * Should you have other questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please send us an email at support@hard69.com
